Hello everyone, can you hear me?
Okay, our live broadcast is about to start in a minute.
Tonight, I will show you how to change the basic half-body dress from the basic half-body dress to some design clothes.
This is the basic half-body dress.
Thank you for watching.
We will see you in the next video.
Good-bye.
Okay, let's start tonight's live broadcast.
Today, we will bring you a basic group of people, and then make some changes.
If you change it, we can bring you four groups of people tonight.
The group of people mainly has a black leather dress like this.
Then there is a full-fledged half-body dress with pleats.
Then there is a full-fledged dress with pleats.
Okay, let's get started.
Before we make the version, let's open a basic group of people file.
Let's open a basic group of people file.
We will share this file with you later.
You can make your own version based on the content of this class.
After we import the version, we want to import a reference picture in the group.
We can draw a larger version next to it.
After drawing the version, we apply a single piece of fabric to it.
Then we drag it into our drawing.
Now, we can do a shrink to fit here.
Then we can make a reference picture here.
Next, I would like to make a reverse reaction or a hidden version of the aquí file.
Ok, search the smile section.
In it, the sample conflicts with I imperial style.
So let's强强跳棱 It's awesome.
As you can see, the basic version has some shortcuts, and the original version also has this shortcut, and the front version has some divisions, and there are some versions that need to be extended to such a joint version.
Let's take a look. First of all, this part is about the division of a production.
We can see a comparison of it. First of all, we can select the group length, select the group length, and make it an extension. We can use the edit version tool to lengthen.
At the same time, we can right-click and enter a specific parameter to adjust it.
For example, we enter 200 and confirm it. You can see that our skirt is stretched by 200 mm.
Next, we can draw the design line on our board. We can use our internal line tool.
You can see this skirt.
This is an arc, so we draw a reference line with a right angle first.
After drawing the top, you can see that the bottom is also a symmetrical structure.
We also make a drawing at the bottom.
The same goes for the back.
We can see that when we make a drawing on the 2D board, as long as we put the two boards together, we will have some auxiliary lines
that can make the internal part of our drawing.
We can see that the line is even.
We can see that we can adjust the position of our line according to our reference picture.
OK, then, some positions are not aligned to the edge of the board, we can align them.
Select this point and right-click to align.
Then we adjust the length of the side opening.
We will make a Ав solve in onze from the важ below.
We can see that the reference board is shaped like an arc.
We can find our edit, we can find our smooth curve tool
Then select our point to make it smooth
Then we select this point and pull it at the same time
You can right-click and click on it
And then we can enter the first and second lines according to the length of the circle
Then we can enter specific parameters here
We click to confirm
You can also adjust its bend rate here
Okay, we turn the next few rectangles into such a round shape
Because the panels are linked, so we just need to adjust one side
Then the next step is to select these lines that we have set up
Then cut and sew them and turn them into segmented panels
OK, then we can adjust the shape of our curve line
On our side, you can select the top and bottom lines to adjust together
Of course, you can also adjust it with our 3D window using our edit noise reduction tool
Let's make the top side of our curve more even
Now we are done with our 3D model
Let's go to the next step
Next, we will work with our round shape
We can draw lines on the straight side like this
Here are the lines we perform the round shape
And then we can adjust the level of the curve
So the number of lines in this circle is just like this
This is our자
The top part of our circle will be in this way
Here are the lines in this circle
All the lines in this circle are in this way
We can adjust the height of the line
Move up and down, we can select it together
We will shorten its distance
Next, we want to merge the side panels
Let it become a whole panel
Then we can select the two sides using the edit panel tool
Then right-click on the line and select merge
This is a very common tool when we change the panel
We can use the 3D window panel to adjust the panel
Next, we will extend the panel
We can say that
We can use this extension panel tool
The extension panel tool needs to select the top of the panel that needs to be extended
This extension panel line needs to select our top of the panel
Then select its bottom
Then we can talk about the dialogue box of the extension panel
Here we choose the direction of the extension as all
We can enter its moving distance
Spread our panels to achieve the effect of our speed
You can see that I have set different sizes here
For example
If we put the top of the panel, it will open up the top of the panel
If we put the bottom of the panel, it will open up the bottom of the panel
If you want to make a lantern style
We can extend the length of line 1
If we want to make a lotus leaf panel
We can extend the length of line 2
Ok, we click on confirm
After confirming, we select these two panels
In the 3D window
You can see that its panels are crossing each other
For example, in the 3D window, we can select this panel
Then you can add this panel to the side
Then we can see
Then we can simulate
You can see that our panels are like the leaf panels
If in the process of operation
It feels that this panel is too large or too small
Then you can use the extension panel tool just used
Choose these two edges again
Then select the direction for all
For example, we choose 300 here
You can see that it is outwards
For example
If you change the value of the value here to negative value, it will reduce the amount.
For example, we now feel that this amount is too large.
We are using the extension board to select the two lines we just selected.
Let's do it again.
We can change its moving distance to negative value, for example, negative 150.
You can see that this board has been reduced by a part.
Just reduce its amount.
In this way, after a few simple steps,
we have changed the half-body group into the effect we want.
Next, we will make some details for it.
For example, its waist has some kind of flight effect.
To make the flight effect in Clover,
we can first make an internal line on the board.
For example, we select the edge of the board.
Before that, I will adjust the waist height of the board.
And at this moment, we can have a very smooth feel.
OK
Then we can select the top of the Lorin's
Then we show the RPM setting here.
In this case, you can see the shape of the line here.
Then go back to the whereas setting.
So we can see the difference.
Let me show you another example.
OK speaking to shift and commission.
The next step is to use a piece of fabric, this is a small sheepskin style, then we find our small sheepskin fabric in the library and apply it to our clothes.
You can see that there are some sheepskin patterns on it, then we can use the edit pattern tool to enlarge it and make the pattern a little thicker.
You can also fill in the color and make a color adjustment.
Click apply, then we can adjust the strength of the hair line and change the type of fabric to leather.
OK.
Then let's find our sheepskin.
When we make clothes with a sheepskin like this, there will be some bumps on the shoulder pads.
At this time, you can use the tool to click on the shoulder pads and then we will simulate it.
OK.
Some of you said that the novice can't understand it, it doesn't matter, we will share the basic version with you.
You can follow the video later.
Then we click on the shoulder pads.
OK.
Adjust the roughness of the fabric, contrast, and so on.
Next, we use our free thread tool to select our panel and add it.
After adding, we can select the thread at the object window and find the roughness of the thread in the water line editor.
For example, we can adjust the thickness of the thread, the length of the thread, the thickness of the thread, the color of the thread, and the diameter of the thread.
In this way, we can add this panel to both sides.
We can also add the position of the bottom of the panel.
Next, we copy the line and adjust the diameter of the line.
For example, change it to 1 and apply it to the waist.
Next, we copy the line and adjust the length of the line.
Next, we copy the line and adjust the thickness of the line and increase the quality of the fabric.
Next, we copy the color of the pattern in the
model
In this way, the first style is finished.
This is a relatively simple style.
Next, let's start making the second style.
Similarly, we will import the basic file.
After that, we will create a template just like before,
and put our reference picture in it.
This is the first style.
This style is a front piece.
We have changed its shape.
We have made an asymmetrical division in the front.
There will be some draw designs.
You can see how this skirt is changed from the basic version in Clo.
In the same way, we will reverse activate the template and hide it.
Next, let's start adjusting.
First, we select the bottom plate and extend it.
It is a skirt that reaches the ankle position.
We can enter a parameter.
It can be slightly larger.
When you are changing the style, you don't need to be so precise.
You can extend it according to your own design feeling.
Stretch it to the length you need.
When the template is out of the back,
you can fix it.
Next, let's move to the waist.
As you can see, this skirt has a waist and a waist strap.
We need to move the waist strap.
Let's see how to do it.
We select the waist strap on both sides of the border plate tool.
Right-click on the waist strap.
You can select the rotation waist strap.
After selecting the rotation waist strap,
you need to select the starting point of the waist strap.
For example, I will select the starting point of the waist strap.
I will move the waist strap to the bottom plate position.
Right-click on the bottom plate position.
Then point to the starting point of the waist strap.
After selecting the starting point of the waist strap,
we can move the waist strap with the mouse.
Let's do it again.
At this time, you can see that the waist strap is selected.
It will become a yellow area.
You can move the waist strap.
It can be rotated.
For example, I move it to the right.
You can see that the waist strap is directly integrated with the waist strap.
Then at this time,
you need to determine the waist strap after you move it.
Then we just pull it to the bottom.
Because we just move it to the bottom plate.
Then remove it.
OK.
Similarly,
if you want to deal with the back piece,
it is also the same operation method.
OK.
We are in the 3D window.
Let's do a reset 3D arrangement of this plate.
Then let's simulate.
Then you can see that the waist strap is sewn.
After it is transferred to the bottom piece,
there is also a seam.
We delete the seam line.
That's it.
Then you can see that it has some more points like this.
We can delete the seam line directly
and then use the edit curve tool
to adjust the shape of the plate.
OK.
What's next?
I feel that after the transfer of the plate in front of me,
its A-shape is more obvious.
I want to turn it into a recessed one.
I want to talk about the entire side seam line.
For this,
we make a rotation.
At this time,
we can use our editing sheet tool.
There is a tool named the editing dot line on the left and right side.
This tool is rarely used.
Its advantage is that it can choose
the points and lines that we need to turn.
Here it is multi-point.
For example,
I want to choose multiple dotted lines.
Then you can see that it has a circle on the outer wheel.
At the center point of the frame,
we can double-click to activate the center point.
Then you can move the center point
to the position you need with the center point.
For example,
I change to the side seam,
then I choose an extra point here.
For example, I choose the entire side line, and then double-click the center point, move the center point to this position, and you can see that it can rotate with this center point.
The advantage of this is that I can both keep the shape of the arc on the side and adjust the line.
OK, we can see that the front of this asymmetric skirt is an arc-shaped shape, a bit like a flower petal, which is a shape that comes over.
We can first un-match this plate.
When doing this kind of asymmetric plate,
you will find that the shape of the pattern is different.
So let's un-match it first.
After un-matching, let's draw a separation line for the front of the skirt.
We can draw a shape line first.
OK.
After drawing, let's un-match this plate.
We can choose a symmetrical plate and un-match it.
After un-matching, let's sew this plate onto our clothes.
In this way, there are two layers in front of us.
What I just used is a symmetrical plate.
A symmetrical plate can be copied and un-matched, but it will not un-match its sewing plate.
OK.
Notice that I am using a symmetrical plate here.
Let's sew it together.
Here, you can choose to sew its side seam together with the back seam,
or you can choose to sew its side seam together with the front seam.
OK.
You can see that there are two layers in front of us.
Then, we cut it according to the line we just designed,
and delete the excess plate.
You can see that we get a line like this.
We get a symmetrical design with the bottom part of the plate.
OK.
Let's sew the front waist part together.
Then, it should be on the right side.
Let's pull out the right side.
OK.
Next, let's design the front plate.
There is a draw plate.
Then, let's choose to draw the draw line.
You can see that it needs to be sewed on the plate at the bottom.
Let's un-match the plate first.
Because when it un-matches,
the line we draw is only on one side.
We need to make a symmetrical sewing of the line at the bottom.
A symmetrical copy.
We choose this line.
Give it Ctrl-C and Ctrl-R.
It is a symmetrical copy.
You can see that it needs to be stitched.
Put it on the strip.
Let's stick it.
Let's take a look at the purpose of this operation.
The line at the bottom is already symmetrical.
Then, I will cut off the top piece.
Then, I can delete the excess.
After I delete it,
I will need a stitch.
So, I will stitch the position that I just saw.
Then, we sew along with
the cut-off piece and the line below.
You can see that we sewed it here.
Let's sew it up.
After sewing it up, we're going to design its output.
For example, I'm going to shorten the position of the sewing point below.
In this way, we'll have a shrink.
When we shrink, we can select the middle line and right-click to select.
Change the length.
You can enter a specific length here.
Click OK.
OK.
Then you can see that there is a shrink effect here.
Let's lower the particle diameter here a little bit.
Otherwise, the effect of this shrink is not very obvious.
You can see that there is such an effect here.
And then we'll take a look.
If we want to continue to increase the shrinkage of the previous piece,
we can use this extension plate tool.
It can select our line and expand it.
It's a bit like when we're making a board shape.
You cut the board shape.
And then we're going to cut the position of this board shape.
After the board is cut, it moves to both sides.
And then you increase the amount.
This is one of the steps.
You can see that, for example, I add so much amount to it.
Then we'll simulate it.
Here, you can also change the length.
There are two ways to make a shrink.
Just like the one before.
OK.
We can see that in this place, we'll add the amount of this board shape.
Then the shrink effect in the front will be more.
The effect is more obvious.
You can see that in both ways.
You can adjust the shape of our board.
make a simple V-shape, and then speed it up.
Okay, now we're going to make the waist two layers.
Then we're going to make the back a little bit narrower,
so that it's a little bit narrower at the bottom.
Okay, and then here, we're going to use a silk fabric like this,
and then we're going to apply it to our board.
Okay, and then we're going to reduce the diameter of the plate again,
and then we're going to make the front of this,
so that the foldable foldable foldable is more obvious.
Adjust a color.
Okay, here, what we're going to do is,
when we're dealing with our foldable clothing,
there are some, for example, there are some foldable places,
that our foldable shape, even if the linear gradient is very low,
We can't do our foldable very well.
In this case, we can select this edge,
and then in our attribute list,
you can find the foldable tool.
The foldable tool, then,
can make our foldable effect more obvious in this place.
Let's open the simulation and take a look
After the rotation of the pointer tool, we can see that the pointer is not at the end
You can select its extension and extend it to the two sides of our board
Then you can adjust the length of our pointer
Its interval is 1 mm
Then let's simulate
You can see that the paper work in this place will be more delicate
Then you can see that the paper work in this place will be more delicate
OK, now we have created the effect of this board
You can practice it according to the practice files we provide
OK, next
Let's start the third version of the modification
The third one is a short skirt
There are some folds on it
Let's see how to make a short skirt like this in Clo
Let's make a G-shaped board
Then we put our text in it
As our reference picture
Let's put the vibrance
OK
In the forward position of the hip survival pattern
There is no way to save theanno
We need the stretching
Så 先来选中我们省蛋的两边
Let's put the string in the corner of the distortor
We need to make a transfer
像刚刚的操作一样
On the right-hand side, select Rotate Curve, select the edge we need to rotate, and then select the length after extension.
The second step is to do the same with the back piece.
Rotate both the front and back pieces to a state of no extension.
In the same way, rotate the bottom piece to the position of the extension, and delete the extra points.
You can also turn it into a free curve point, and then adjust it.
After the extension is completed, select the two panels in the 3D window, right-click on the panel, and select Rearrange 3D Array Position.
Then do a simulation.
Rotate the back piece to a free curve point with a straight line.
In this way, we have turned the front and back pieces into a state of no extension.
We can see in this reference picture,
the skirt has a flat surface in the front,
and there are several folds in the position near the side seam.
Let's see how to make such a style in Clo.
At this time, we need to use a fold tool.
In the 2D window, you can see the position of my mouse pointer.
It is a fold tool.
We find it, select the fold tool,
and then select the fold tool.
The way to use the fold tool is that we need to choose two sides.
One is the starting point of the fold,
and the other is the end point of the fold.
We click one side and point to the other side.
After the demonstration is completed, we click it,
and it will pop up the dialogue box of our fold.
You can see that there are three types of folds in the fold.
There are those who follow, those who follow, and those who follow.
Below, it will have the corresponding fold specifications.
For example, the number of folds, the width of the fold, and the diameter of the fold.
We can see that below the number, it has the beginning and the end.
This refers to the width of the beginning and the end of the fold.
For example, some folds,
it may say that the position of the front of the waist is 3 cm wide,
and then it may be 4 cm wide or 5 cm wide after extending to the bottom.
Here we can set the beginning and the end to different widths
to achieve the effect of extending the fold.
Here, I first enter its beginning.
For example, I can add three folds here.
You can see that on the right side of the beginning and the end,
there is such a small arrow.
There is such a locked mark.
If it is default, it is locked.
It is a link mark.
For example, when I enter the beginning, it will move with the end.
You can click on this mark.
It is not locked together.
You can adjust the beginning and the end separately.
You can see that the beginning and the end here are set to different widths.
It will show up at the 2D window.
For example, here I set the beginning to 20 and the end to 50.
You can see that there are different effects below.
You can see that here we have a maximum value.
If you set this parameter to exceed the maximum value,
there is no way to generate a discount.
When the discount is generated,
it is based on the amount of the remaining sheets.
For example, we choose the position of the discount from a point.
For example, the length of this sheet is only 60 cm.
For example, you want to set 5 discounts.
Each discount is wide.
For example, you have 60 cm left.
If each discount is 10 cm wide,
you can set 6 discounts.
If each discount is 12 cm wide,
you can only set 5 discounts.
It is based on the amount you have left.
It is based on the amount you have left to calculate.
OK, then we click OK.
After clicking OK,
we don't do it first.
There is another point here.
When we use our discount tool to create a discount,
we must sew the sheet.
Because the sheet after sewing,
it can be based on the sheet after sewing.
You create a discount again.
Your discount will automatically generate a discount line.
You don't need to do it again.
This should be noted.
OK, then we put the discount sheet in the 3D window.
Rearrange the 3D arrangement position.
Then give it a hardening simulation.
Remember that our discount must be hardened.
In this way, we can see that the position in the front
generates a three-fold effect like this.
Let's adjust the particle scale first.
OK, we can see that we made a short-circuit effect
by making a discount like this quickly.
Next, we can make some details for it.
For example, I want to extend the position of the side seam.
I want to extend the position of the side seam.
Continue to extend it and make it bigger.
You can use the extension panel tool to adjust it.
OK.
Next, let's change the straight line of the side seam.
to adjust the shape of the curve.
Next, let's adjust the curve of the bottom plate.
Here, it has a lot of straight lines.
Let's convert it to a free curve point.
Next, let's see if we are adjusting the length of the plate.
For example, I feel that this folding group is a bit long.
I want it to be shorter.
Then you can choose the bottom plate of our plate.
Then choose our plate outline expansion.
We all know that this plate outline expansion tool can expand outward.
But very few people know that it can shrink inward.
For example, we choose this direction.
Change its extension to shrink.
You can see that it becomes like this.
Then we directly input a shrink paper.
For example, we need to shrink its bottom plate to 20 cm or 30 cm.
Then you can enter a specific parameter.
For example, I enter 30 mm here.
You can see that it shrinks inward by 30 mm.
Enter 40 mm and it can shrink inward by 40 mm.
The advantage of this is that we need to create an inner line for it.
Then cut and sew it.
Then delete the board.
In this way, we only need one tool to complete it.
OK.
Then we convert the excess straight line point into a free line point.
Then we don't need to worry about the straight line that comes out.
Let's adjust the shape of the arc first.
Then you can use the edit board tool.
Choose our extension.
Select the inner line.
Then directly right-click to add it.
Then it has a symmetry to the outside line of the board.
Then align it to the outside line of the board.
Then it's OK.
OK.
Next, we can see that there is such a shape division in the bottom plate.
Let's create such a shape division for it.
Here, I choose to shrink it.
Keep it short.
Select the inner line diameter.
A bit shorter.
I need to shrink it 20 mm.
Don't be too strict.
OK.
We can see that there is such a shape division in the reference picture of this board.
Then we select the bottom plate line.
Right-click to select the inner line diameter.
Let's create an inner line of 80 mm for it.
Then we click on confirm.
After confirming, we need to create such a shape here.
This is the fold effect of the top and bottom凹凸.
Let's see if there is any simple operation method.
Here we can use the plus point tool.
We can actually use the plus point division tool.
Right-click on this line.
Then you can choose the average division.
For example, we give it an average division of about 9 sections.
Then click OK.
In this way, the middle line is the same width.
This side is also the same.
After we add this tool,
you can directly select the point we have added.
Then move it up and down.
Then let it produce this zero angle effect.
The back side is the same.
The back side is also the same.
It's a bit different.
OK, then we can choose the inner line we just created.
Directly do the inner line division.
For example, we give it an average of about 30.
Then click OK.
OK, then we will make some alignments of the line produced, such as the alignment to the edge, the adjustment of the side seam, and the adjustment of the front and back seam.
Next, we can select these two lines and make a cut-and-sew.
OK, now we have the cut-and-sew for the front.
Next, we will apply a fabric to the line.
We will apply a fabric to the line.
OK, now we will apply a fabric to the line.
There is a button here
Let's see how to make a button like this
First of all
We want to extend it to the position of the side gap
But our waist is a whole piece connected together
We want to separate this place
Separate it
It's very simple
We found our one in the 3D window
Modification line tool
You can see that it can be easily separated in our 3D window
Then we can select the point that needs to be separated
Then go to the other side
Then double click
It will cut our 2D version
After cutting
Let's make this little version
We can take a look at the width of our waist
For example, its width is 35.2
Let's use the curve tool to make a height of 35.2
And then if it's wide
We can set it to 80 points first
Then we can add a straight line on one side
Then
Let it come out
In this way
We become such a
Healing tip head-shaped tablet
How do we choose the whole line bar at the same time
That is, you can double click on this line
Add it to the outside
Make a split
What are your preferences
Let's see how it works.
Okay, let's simulate it and drag it back with our hands.
After dragging it back, we need a buckle here.
We can fix it with a pin like this.
After fixing it, because we are designing it now,
so there are no holes in the position,
we can determine the position of the upper and lower position
by the position of the pin.
For example, we can add a button to the lower position.
Then we can find the position of the buckle on the upper position.
Then we can use the button tool to tie them together.
The pin is no longer used, so we delete it.
You can see that we added the buckle to it.
Then we can, because we are symmetrical on both sides,
we can directly select the symmetrical plate, plate and sewing line on the right side of it
and copy it.
After copying it,
because we only have one side of the button,
so we can use the button tool to select our button.
On the right side of the button,
there is a plate called copy, symmetry, and modification.
As long as the two sides are symmetrical,
it can copy the button.
Then we add a button to the lower position.
At the bottom, we need to add a button to the upper position.
For example, we need to let it copy.
We can use the button tool.
Or, we can put it in the center of the button.
In the learning of sewing,
I like the position of the button.
We can add the undivided button,
and the button is fixed.
Then we add the button to the upper position.
On the left, there is a button to the upper position.
We can add the button to the lower position.
The particle diameter of this plate will be lowered a little bit.
This will not affect the overall effect of our system.
But it can make it more stable.
Next, let's take a look at how to make an invisible zipper in our skirt.
Let's take a look at how to make an invisible zipper.
For example, we open the zipper at the back waist.
Then we cut the back piece of the zipper.
Let's start to simulate.
Next, we shorten the back piece of the zipper.
For example, we shorten it to this position.
Let's take a look at it first.
It's a little bit high, so let's make it a little bit lower.
For this side, we can use our 3D zipper tool directly.
Then you choose one side, double click, and then double click at the end to finish.
You can see why I just added a dot at the back piece of the zipper.
Because when we make an invisible zipper,
if you have a dot, it can go to this point.
It's more convenient to have a dot to choose from.
Then we double click on the other side.
You can see that we have added this 3D zipper.
After the 3D zipper is added, what do we do with the invisible zipper?
It's very simple.
You just need to choose your zipper.
We can adjust the width of our zipper and zipper here in the attribute editor.
We can change the width of the zipper and zipper to the first point.
For example, first, we can change your zipper to a 1.
Then the zipper can be changed to a 2.
You can see that the zipper is very small and very thin.
It looks like an invisible zipper.
At this point, we just need to select our zipper and the lower lip.
For example, we don't need the lower lip.
You can right-click on the lip and select display to hide it and hide the lower lip.
Then we can select the position of the waist, its zipper and zipper.
Then select the shape of our more common invisible zipper zipper and zipper.
Then adjust it a little bit.
In this way, we can create an invisible zipper effect.
Okay, the next step is to use our fabric.
In the drawing, we find an invisible fabric and apply it.
After applying, we can change its color.
Then we can copy a few pieces of the fabric.
Then we can color it.
For example, we can use a white color for this piece of fabric in the middle.
Then we can copy the position of the bottom.
Then we can color it.
For example, when we are making this kind of fold effect, the edge of its fold line looks like the grid is not very even.
At this time, we can use a tool, that is, we can select these fold lines.
Select these fold lines, and then we right-click on the line and select the internal line diameter.
Then you can select its expansion number in the internal line diameter.
For example, the diameter here, we usually set it to 2 mm, and then you can choose.
There is a two-sided in the option, we will connect the two sides, and then we click to confirm.
In this way, we have a two-sided, which means that we have set such an over-angle on both sides,
so that the fold position looks more comfortable and more beautiful.
This is a little trick.
Next, let's adjust the color of the eye.
Next, we select these fold lines and adjust the particle diameter for it.
Then we can add some details to it.
For example, the line of sight, and so on.
We use the line of sight tool to add it to the bottom plate.
Here, in the bottom plate position, I can add a circle of this kind of hand needle effect.
Here, we set the thickness of the line of sight to be slightly higher.
Then, we set the thickness of the line of sight to be slightly higher.
We set the color of the line of sight and a diameter of the line of sight and a diameter.
For example, 40 mm foraging, which is 4 mm,
you can see that there will be such a line of sight effect in this bottom plate.
You can see this magical effect.
There was such a foldable bag,
and insert the template into it
the same way as the basic template
just like the previous step
we will create a template
and insert our reference image into it
after adding the internal line
we will simulate it
and then we will use the reference image
to create a reference image
Ok
This is the long skirt effect
that we are going to create
the front side will be
a asymmetrical design
and there will be a three-dimensional pocket
and below the pocket
there will be a loop
among which we will set
the inner layer of the skirt
into two-sided one
There will be an effect of the wind-sweeper on the right side.
Let's see how this kind of skirt can be realized by changing the version in Claw.
OK, then we will adjust this version in the same way.
First of all, we select the bottom line and make it longer.
It's a little bit longer than the middle line.
It's a little bit longer.
It's a little bit slanted.
Let's simulate it.
After the simulation, let's take a look at this version.
We still have to make a path transfer in the front.
Let's select our path and make a path transfer first.
Use the edit tool to select our path.
Then right-click and select Rotate Path.
Then left-click and select Rotate Path.
Then we select the back to make a path transfer.
Then let's adjust the first layer of the bottom line.
Then select these two panels in the 3D window and reset the 3D arrangement position
Then we will simulate
In this way, we will quickly turn the rope over
After turning it over, we can take a look at this skirt
In front of it, there is such an irregular style
Let's try it
Let's use the button to adjust the length of the side
Next, we need to draw the separation line on the panel
You can see that it is from the position of the cross section to the front
First, because there is such an irregular piece in the front
Let's copy the position of the front piece first
Put it aside and keep it for later use
Then we use the inner line tool to draw the shape of the corner
OK
After we draw these two reference lines
We can freely adjust the position of the line
To reach the state we want
It's a little bit high here
Let's move it down a little bit
OK
After we have determined these two lines
We select our line and cut it off
OK
Let's cut this piece down
After cutting it down, the next step is to give it to it first
We can adjust it in 3D via the 3D tool here
OK
This way you can see the line is on the both sides of the panel
Let's take a look at these two panels
We need to put it in a fold
A production of a fold
Then we also use our fold tool
Select our side
Click on one side
Then point to the position of our bottom
Then choose the direction of the fold to extend
We choose the top and bottom of the paper, and we choose the slope here.
Then I will enter the width of our fold, and I will enter its number first.
For example, I enter 15 folds here, and then I will make its end position a little wider.
Then I will enter 15 folds here, and then I will make its end position a little wider.
OK, we click OK.
You can see that we put the fold and the number here.
Next, we choose the back of the paper, and we use the same method to make it.
OK, we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we choose the fold and the number here, and then we
Let's create a 3D layout
We can't do it directly
If we do it directly, the fight will be more intense
And then
Let's add it to the side
Or something like that
And then print it
As you can see
There will still be some fights here
And then let's make these two panels
Rearrange the 3D layout
And then let's make it
Let's make this folding panel
Don't get in the way of the other panels
Pull it a little further
Then it will be more stable
The front and back of the panel
Are not merged into one
They are divided into two
If you are practicing
You can merge it into a whole
OK
And then
Let's make it harder
Pay attention
When making folding panels
You have to make it harder
To simulate the pattern
That is to say
It will be better
OK
Next
Let's make the front part of the skirt
First
Let's make its waist higher
Let's make it 10 mm
That is 1 cm higher
Let's make the waist higher
OK
Then let's find the front part
Let's remove the joint first
Then first
Let's determine the shape of the front part
Let's draw one at a time
That's about it
Then let's cut this side
And delete the rest
After that
The front part
Has a waist on the front
We can adjust this panel
For example
Let's delete this curve point
And then
Expand the panel
Expand to a height
As high as the waist
Let's measure it
Expand the panel
And then
Let's determine the center
We can use a hole-in-circle tool
To cut it and sew it
Then we can make a waist
For this panel
Then we can sew the side of
The panel
And the top
Arrange it
In front of the suit
Move it
Pull it
OK
You can see that you can drag this board over
And then when you drag it, if it's not stable and it falls down, you can add a fixing pin to it
Ah, the fast key to the fixing pin is the W key, which means you can select the board and then press W to add such a fixing pin
Okay, so we're going to make sure it's in a position
And then we're going to cut it open here and we're going to use our one like we did in the beginning
I'm going to kllear the
Then I'm going to give it a little bend and then I'm going to make the back of the side
Aha ha!
Let me tell you a little trick here.
Why do we need to add a button here instead of an eye button?
We can use our edge button tool.
For example, the front and back layers of our board have been selected.
At this time, we don't know where the button is.
After adding the button, right-click on the button and select the settings layer.
The default setting is to hit a point from the bottom of the button.
Then, the two positions are fixed together.
Let's simulate it.
Here, since there is no eye button, we can make sure that it can be fixed together.
This is a quick tool that can quickly make our button to be fixed on our material.
At this time, let's adjust the shape of the front.
Then, we set an inner line border for the position of the waist.
The next layer is the same.
OK.
We see this on our board.
We give it a close-up.
connotation material reflection 40
Then we make this boardiu
Here is a solution for making a close-up with your adhe.
I use this many times.
We set the compositor afterwards,
Then I make the board to position ho cómo
And I select the curves around the board.
This is the edge you need to hide, and then directly hide it as a board
If you can see this, we have got a side-by-side shape
Then we sew this board to our clothing
Ok, now we have added the side-by-side effect to this board
Next, we apply the fabric on it
Here I use an oblique cotton fabric
Make it a little bit harder
Then we use the side-by-side fabric to make it look like this
First, we use an organza fabric
Then we adjust the transparency of the organza fabric to make it a little bit less transparent
Next, we can select the inside of the board
If we select the inside line
There are many inside lines on this foldable board
I want to select it once and operate it
Then you can press it four times on the line
You can select all the inside lines on the board
We select these inside lines and then open its foldable rendering
Ok, next, let's take a look at the production of this organza pocket
Here, because we don't have the size of the pocket
We can design it according to our own design
For example, I will draw a G shape first
Take a look at its size and position
For example, I feel it is a little small
Then you can enlarge it a little bit
A little bit bigger
Ok, after this is determined
We can
Directly right-click on the G shape we have designed
Select the Cologne board
We got a board like this
Next, let's take a look at this board
How to make it into a three-dimensional pocket
We can select the two sides of the board
Then right-click to select the board outline expansion
For example, it expands to 30 mm or 20 mm
We click OK
Then at the same time I select the bottom board
Then expand the board outline again
You can see that it is extended again
You can see that it has become a shape similar to our box
In this way
I select the three sides
Select it and then transform it into a line
Then we can find it here in the three-dimensional window
Then we can use the three sides that we just extended
Use our folding arrangement tool to fold it back
It becomes a box shape
At this point, it's very easy
Just use the sewing tool to sew up its three sides
Then sew the corner on the side
OK, then let's simulate it
You can see that this pocket is sitting up
OK, here, because the top of the pocket is not folded
We can fold it manually
We can add a inner line to the side of our board
You can see that a new inner line is added here
Then both sides are
After adding
We can set this inner line to a fold angle
After adding, we can set this inner line to a fold angle
I drew a little asymmetric in both sides
When you're drawing, you have to draw it in the same way
Select it to make it look inward or outward
In this way, our ancient model will look better
Then at this time
Let's make a belt cover
A belt cover is much easier
We just select this inner curve
And then we have to close the screen
And then we can close the screen
And then
If the curve on our clothing
We can give it an inner line
Create a sewing line for the inner line
Create a sewing line
For example, give it a line of 10, no need to extend it in the opposite direction
In this case, let's make it a little bit shorter
Then we sew it up directly
Then we simulate it
You can see that in this way, we have a cover for this costume
Let's extend it a little bit again
Here, you can use your own inspiration to freely adjust the position and size of your board
In this case, we set its internal line diameter
Then sew it up internally
OK, then we can add two buttons on the belt
The button gives us
The front is the same
After adding the button, select these two buttons directly
Then right-click on the button and select the sewing layer
Then set the sewing layer to two layers
Then click OK
You can see that it is directly pointed to the belt
OK, then let's make it under the belt
There is such a hanging ring
This is also very simple to make
We just need to draw a small long strip
You can draw a little bit smaller here
After drawing a small one
We sew it up
We sew it up on our board
Then we generate an internal line in the middle
Then we sew it up to our costume
The last two points can be sewn in one place
Then here, we use the folding arrangement tool
Fold it
OK, then we simulate it
This is a very small board
Before you simulate it
You can set its example area to a little lower
You can see here it has a string effect
Next, we add a D-cone
In our canvas
We found this ring hole
There is a D-ring inside the ring hole
Then we directly open its link
Then paste it to our position
After pasting it to our position, we can adjust it to this position
After that, we can adjust its size.
For example, when you are making a D-shaped buckle or a ring,
For example, I want it to pull the fabric down like the real one.
For example, it has a gravity effect.
Then you can select your component from the object window.
Then you can adjust its weight on the right side.
For example, let's increase the weight a little bit.
You can see that it will naturally pull the fabric down.
OK.
In this way, we have made a general version of this costume.
Next, we can adjust some of the details in it.
For example, the shape of the button, the material of the button,
and the color of the fabric.
OK.
Next, let's adjust the color of the fabric and add some details.
For example, add some lines and adjust the material color of the fabric.
At this time,
we will talk about the content of today's live broadcast.
For example, we will talk about the content of today's live broadcast.
Next, we can answer some questions.
If you have any questions,
please leave a message in the message area.
please come forward and answer them in this second part of the talk.
In the case of the ring for the waiting line for upper portion material,
you do not have to insulted to let from.
Because it is modified along with our fabric.
If you are wearing a real ring, you need to open the screen to see the real ring.
Let's change the position of the clothes.
You can make another lining in the organza.
We are not going to show the making of the lining.
Let me tell you one more thing.
When the organza is rendering, the 3D window and the rendering window have some differences.
For example, the 3D window may be very transparent.
But when rendering, it is based on the real physical properties of the light.
It may not be so transparent when rendering.
If your clothing is rendering, you can adjust it mainly by rendering.
Let me change the color and render it for you.
Let's examine the 3D window.
We see a 3D window for the light.
The 3D window is black.
It is not transparent, so we can't see the light.
But the light is transparent when rendering.
The light is black.
The red line is white.
The red line is blue.
The light is black.
The red line is white.
The green line is blue.
The red line is yellow.
As you can see, the material of the 3D window looks more transparent, but it is not as transparent when it is rendered.
This is the content of today.
Some students asked about how to use the folding tool. Let's take a look again.
Some students asked about how to add a component to the 3D model. Let's take a look at the folding tool.
For example, I create a rectangle here.
The width and height of the rectangle are 50 cm.
Click OK.
For the principle of folding, let's divide it into equal parts.
As you can see, the diameter of each part is 100 mm.
For example, let's use the folding tool.
For the folding tool, let's use the folding tool directly.
Select the point of the top of the panel.
For example, I want to extend it downwards.
Then you point it downwards.
At this time, you need to select the side that needs to be folded.
For example, I need to fold the right side.
Right?
Click OK on the left side.
OK.
At this time, we will start to enter the width of each fold.
The width of the fold here is calculated according to the remaining volume of the panel.
For example, the total width of this panel is 50 cm.
Then we fold to the right from the first point.
That is, the left side has removed 10 cm.
The rest is only 40 cm.
Right?
At this time, let's change its start.
Here, I change it to 100.
That is, 100 mm for each fold.
For example, we have 400 mm left.
Then we only add 4 folds.
If you want to add more, you can see that you can add 5 folds.
If you add more, you can't add more.
Because it is added according to the remaining amount.
Pay attention.
At this time, you need to shrink and click OK.
After clicking OK, you can see that these folds are not sewn.
We click the sewing line.
It is not sewn.
So you still need to sew this fold by yourself.
But if we are creating a fold,
I will give you a simple example.
For example, when we are creating a fold,
my panel is already sewn up and down.
You can take a look.
OK.
Then I will create a fold from this basis.
For example, I will enter its width and the number of folds.
Click OK.
OK.
At this time, we will print it.
Let's simulate it again.
You can see that here,
its fold automatically has a seam relationship.
See?
So when you are using the fold tool to make a fold,
you must first sew your panel.
After sewing, we will continue to make it.
Then next,
some students will encounter that
there will be some folds in the fold I made.
It seems that the grid is irregular.
You can choose the line above us.
In the panel,
there will be a fold line.
We open it.
You can see that its edge will be straighter and more regular.
If we want to choose all the lines on the panel,
you can press 4 times on one line.
1, 2, 3, 4.
Then it can choose all the lines.
We open the fold line again.
You can see that here,
we have a very regular fold.
Let's unseal it.
OK.
This is how we use the fold.
Yes.
The one with the seam and the one with the seam.
It's just that we are choosing a different fold.
For example, let me choose one again.
You can see that
you choose the one with the seam, the one with the seam, and the one with the seam.
It will help you to set different folding angles.
But the methods are the same.
Then our top 1 version will be in the next live broadcast.
It will bring you the version about the top 1.
The main part of this episode is about the version about the half-fold.
OK.
Do you have any other questions?
No.
All right.
Thank you.
Have a good day.
Bye bye.
See you next time.
Let's see how to load a virtual model.
The virtual model is a tool for loading a virtual model.
For example, let's untie this board.
You can find a basic length measurement in our 3D window.
Then there are some surface lengths in the left-hand page.
For example, let's choose the original measurement.
You can draw a cloud line on your model.
For example, we click on its waist and draw a line here.
Then when drawing a line, you can press the Shift key at the same time.
Then double-click three times to create a whole line.
Then we can cooperate with the virtual model.
For example, when we make some clothes,
for example, pants, it always falls down.
Then you can use our second tool,
called virtual model measurement.
Then we select the position where our board needs to be glued.
Select this edge.
Then you can see it.
There is a red line here.
We can simulate it a little bit.
You can see that it is like a sewing machine.
It is sewn to our model.
But it is just a supporting tool.
For example, when we made pants in the early stage,
the pants fell down.
You can absorb it through this tool.
But in the end, you still have to judge why your pants fall.
For example, the waist board is bigger.
Or there is no camera.
Or you need to add some belt.
These parameters are just a supporting tool.
You can't use it all the time.
If we have to add the belt.
The fabric will eventually be bigger or heavier.
It will look much bigger.
If we don't need to adjust the same position.
How to adjust the position?
Here, let me explain it to you.
If the front is slanted.
The back is slanted.
If this part here is slanted.
It will look better.
If this is slanted.
So, the front is slanted.
It will be less slanted.
The back is slanted.
If it is slanted,
it will go down.
If this is slanted,
it will go under.
How can we adjust the position?
It is slanted.
It can go under.
After we add and Lord's fold,
This student asks, how to use the add-on of the butterfly knot?
Let me show you.
When we are making this, when we are using this material,
there is this butterfly knot in the material, right?
There are two files in the butterfly knot.
One is the file called trim.
It is directly added to the work area.
You can directly paste it into your clothing.
Paste it on the clothing. It is a model.
Just stick it here.
See?
But if I want to be like a real butterfly knot,
you can choose the one called clothing file.
Double click to open it.
There are a lot of ZPAC files here.
We can add it to the work area by right-clicking.
These butterfly knots are made up of plates.
It is like a real one.
It is a real butterfly knot.
See?
It is made up of plates.
How to use these?
You can use them according to the real position.
For example, we want to sew it to the position of our waist.
Then you can add a small internal line to the plate of your butterfly knot.
It is the same for our clothing.
Then we can sew the butterfly knot.
For example, we can use the internal line.
OK.
You can see that I choose this butterfly knot.
Move it a little bit.
You can see that it is like a real butterfly knot.
You can sew it to the plate of your butterfly knot.
I am not doing it well.
You know what this tool means.
I should adjust it here.
It should be sewn here.
Let me sew it again.
You can see that it is like a real butterfly knot.
You can see that it can be sewn to our clothing.
This is the second way of processing.
The third way of processing is the first way of sewing.
When you sew, you can only sew the butterfly knot.
You sew the butterfly knot.
You sew the butterfly knot on your sweaters first.
But you need to much process the butterfly knot.
You have to make sure that the butterfly knot is not too deep.
The wave of the butterfly knot is very important.
You need to adjust it.
Next, you might need to adjust the accumulator of your clothing.
You need to reduce the accumulator of your clothing.
Then you increase the emanation of the conflict, then you have to adjust it.
Then you can check your version again.
Okay, that's it for today's live stream.
If you have any questions,
you can leave a message in the official background of Bilibili.
In the next live stream,
we will bring you some changes to our top 1.
Okay, goodbye everyone.